http://www.drugawareness.org/contact/privacypolicy/

Skip to content
Privacy Policy of drugawareness.org
Cookies Privacy Policy
This website stores cookies on your computer. These cookies are used to collect information about how you interact with our website and allow us to remember you. We use this information in order to improve and customize your browsing experience and for analytics and metrics about our visitors both on this website and other media.
drugawareness.org operates the http://www.drugawareness.org/ website, which provides the SERVICE.
This page is used to inform website visitors regarding our policies with the collection, use, and disclosure of Personal Information if anyone decided to use our Service, the International Coalition for Drug Awareness & The Kito Foundation website.
If you choose to use our Service, then you agree to the collection and use of information in relation with this policy. The Personal Information that we collect are used for providing and improving the Service. We will not use or share your information with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy.
The terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions, which is accessible at http://www.drugawareness.org/, unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy.
Information Collection and Use
For a better experience while using our Service, we may require you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information, including but not limited to your name, phone number, and postal address. The information that we collect will be used to contact or identify you.
Log Data
We want to inform you that whenever you visit our Service, we collect information that your browser sends to us that is called Log Data. This Log Data may include information such as your computer’s Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser version, pages of our Service that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages, and other statistics.
Cookies
Cookies are files with small amount of data that is commonly used an anonymous unique identifier. These are sent to your browser from the website that you visit and are stored on your computer’s hard drive.
Our website uses these “cookies” to collection information and to improve our Service. You have the option to either accept or refuse these cookies, and know when a cookie is being sent to your computer. If you choose to refuse our cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Service.
Service Providers
We may employ third-party companies and individuals due to the following reasons:
To facilitate our Service;
To provide the Service on our behalf;
To perform Service-related services; or
To assist us in analyzing how our Service is used.
We want to inform our Service users that these third parties have access to your Personal Information. The reason is to perform the tasks assigned to them on our behalf. However, they are obligated not to disclose or use the information for any other purpose.
Security
We value your trust in providing us your Personal Information, thus we are striving to use commercially acceptable means of protecting it. But remember that no method of transmission over the internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure and reliable, and we cannot guarantee its absolute security.
Links to Other Sites
Our Service may contain links to other sites. If you click on a third-party link, you will be directed to that site. Note that these external sites are not operated by us. Therefore, we strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of these websites. We have no control over, and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies, or practices of any third-party sites or services.
Children’s Privacy
Our Services do not address anyone under the age of 13. We do not knowingly collect personal identifiable information from children under 13. In the case we discover that a child under 13 has provided us with personal information, we immediately delete this from our servers. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your child has provided us with personal information, please contact us so that we will be able to do necessary actions.
Changes to This Privacy Policy
We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. Thus, we advise you to review this page periodically for any changes. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page. These changes are effective immediately, after they are posted on this page.
Contact Us
If you have any questions or suggestions about our Privacy Policy, do not hesitate to contact us.
International Coalition for Drug Awareness & The Kito Foundation
Copyright © 2018 All Rights Reserved
DISCLAIMER: The information included on this site is for educational purposes only. It is not intended nor implied to be a substitute for professional medical advice. The reader should always consult his or her healthcare provider to determine the appropriateness of the information for their own situation or if they have any questions regarding a medical condition or treatment plan. Reading the information on this website does not create a physician-patient relationship.
This site is in no way associated with either the Church of Scientology or the Citizens Commission on Human Rights (CCHR).
FAIR USE NOTICE: This may contain copyrighted © material the use of which has not always been specifically authorized by the copyright owner. Such material is made available for educational purposes, to advance understanding of human rights, democracy, scientific, moral, ethical, and social justice issues, etc. It is believed that this constitutes a ‘fair use’ of any such copyrighted material as provided for in Title 17 U.S.C. section 107 of the US Copyright Law.
Sign up for free essential Oil class
* indicates required
Email Address
*
First Name
Last Name
Birthday
/
( mm / dd )
Drug Awareness, Educating about the dangers of SSRI medications.
Log in
Entries feed
Comments feed
WordPress.org
Follow us now on Twitter and Facebook.Follow @ICFDA
“Our physiology is perfectly designed for bliss and this perfection is dynamic, so taking responsibility for your own health is important.” Candace Pert
Listen/Watch Now
Find out More "Ann B Tracy has boldly gone
where few dare to tread…"
Everything your doctor does not know & drug companies
hope NO ONE ever learns about serotonin & Serotonergic medications (all
antidepressants, atypical anti-psychotics & some pain killers) Also contains information on safe & successful withdrawal.
Click on the book to order
or (801) 901-0818
______________________________
PROZAC: PANACEA OR PANDORA? OUR SEROTONIN NIGHTMARE (Second Edition)
Book Excerpts
BOOK TESTIMONIALS "VERY BOLD AND INFORMATIVE"
"PRICELESS INFORMATION THAT IS GIVING ME BACK TO ME"
"THE ABSOLUTE BEST REFERENCE FOR ANTIDEPRESSANT DRUGS"
"WELL DOCUMENTED &
SCIENTIFICALLY RESEARCHED"
"I was stunned at the amount of research Ann B. Tracy has done on this subject. Few researchers go to as much trouble agressively gathering information on the adverse reactions of Prozac, Zoloft and other SSRIs."
More Book Testimonials
CD/MP3 Help! I can’t get off my antidepressant!
Sign up for updatesFree Drug Awareness News with Ann Blake-Tracy
Name
Email
Hold the FDA accountable.. by reporting adverse side effects to the FDA at Medwatch or 1-800-FDA-1088 (1-800-332-1088). Read more
Search for:
Recent Posts
BREAKING NEWS FROM CDC ON REAL COVID DEATH FIGURES
ANTIDEPRESSANT: Officer Not Charged in Teen Girl Shooting Death
Elvis Presley’s grandson, Benjamin Keough’s girlfriend pleaded with him before ‘he shot himself ‘
Our Real Pandemic: 40% Increase in RX/Serotonin Drug Use & the Aftermath
Join Ann Blake-Tracy *LIVE* May 27, 2020 9:00 pm EST on F.A.C.E.U.S. Radio.
Recent CommentsAnn Blake-Tracy on Ann Blake-Tracy’s September 13, 2004 to the FDATHAILAND: ANTIDEPRESSANTS STRIKE AGAIN!!! 30 TOTAL DEAD IN MASS SHOOTING!!! FAILURE TO WARN OF METABOLISM ISSUES AMONG RACES - International Coalition for Drug Awareness - ICFDA on 1996 – Mutant Mice May Hold Key To Human Violence – An Excess Of Serotonin.NY Machete Attack & How Antidepressants Cause Violence - International Coalition for Drug Awareness - ICFDA on MASS KILLINGS: If You Think It Is Guns You Need to Think Again!!!NY Machete Attack & How Antidepressants Cause Violence - International Coalition for Drug Awareness - ICFDA on 1996 – Mutant Mice May Hold Key To Human Violence – An Excess Of Serotonin.A PERFECT EXAMPLE OF HOMICIDAL IDEATION: Florida Man 'Looking For Someone To Kill' Intentionally Ran Over Veteran With Car - International Coalition for Drug Awareness - ICFDA on 1996 – Mutant Mice May Hold Key To Human Violence – An Excess Of Serotonin.Archives Archives
Select Month
August 2020  (1)
July 2020  (2)
June 2020  (1)
May 2020  (4)
April 2020  (5)
February 2020  (1)
January 2020  (3)
December 2019  (4)
September 2019  (4)
August 2019  (5)
July 2019  (7)
June 2019  (2)
May 2019  (4)
April 2019  (5)
March 2019  (3)
February 2019  (7)
January 2019  (4)
December 2018  (2)
November 2018  (7)
October 2018  (5)
September 2018  (5)
August 2018  (6)
July 2018  (3)
June 2018  (1)
May 2018  (3)
April 2018  (2)
March 2018  (4)
February 2018  (4)
January 2018  (2)
December 2017  (8)
November 2017  (5)
October 2017  (2)
September 2017  (6)
August 2017  (3)
June 2017  (2)
May 2017  (8)
April 2017  (6)
March 2017  (7)
February 2017  (3)
January 2017  (5)
December 2016  (3)
November 2016  (1)
October 2016  (2)
September 2016  (1)
August 2016  (3)
July 2016  (8)
June 2016  (6)
May 2016  (6)
April 2016  (4)
March 2016  (3)
January 2016  (6)
December 2015  (2)
November 2015  (4)
October 2015  (5)
September 2015  (7)
August 2015  (19)
July 2015  (12)
June 2015  (12)
May 2015  (11)
April 2015  (7)
March 2015  (19)
February 2015  (9)
January 2015  (15)
December 2014  (15)
November 2014  (23)
October 2014  (16)
September 2014  (11)
August 2014  (9)
July 2014  (4)
June 2014  (1)
May 2014  (6)
April 2014  (12)
March 2014  (9)
February 2014  (16)
January 2014  (18)
December 2013  (15)
November 2013  (13)
October 2013  (17)
September 2013  (78)
August 2013  (12)
July 2013  (3)
June 2013  (8)
May 2013  (10)
April 2013  (6)
March 2013  (8)
January 2013  (2)
December 2012  (7)
November 2012  (7)
October 2012  (3)
September 2012  (16)
August 2012  (11)
July 2012  (4)
June 2012  (1)
May 2012  (8)
April 2012  (1)
March 2012  (6)
February 2012  (20)
November 2011  (1)
October 2011  (5)
August 2011  (1)
July 2011  (3)
May 2011  (1)
March 2011  (10)
February 2011  (5)
January 2011  (2)
December 2010  (2)
October 2010  (2)
August 2010  (2)
July 2010  (2)
June 2010  (34)
May 2010  (34)
April 2010  (2)
March 2010  (2)
February 2010  (84)
January 2010  (12)
December 2009  (66)
November 2009  (14)
October 2009  (33)
September 2009  (38)
August 2009  (59)
July 2009  (37)
June 2009  (24)
May 2009  (1)
April 2009  (1)
December 2008  (1)
November 2008  (6)
August 2008  (2)
March 2008  (4)
February 2008  (1)
January 2008  (1)
January 2005  (1)
October 2004  (1)
July 2004  (2)
June 2004  (7)
May 2004  (6)
April 2004  (4)
March 2004  (18)
February 2004  (8)
January 2004  (10)
October 2003  (1)
September 2003  (5)
August 2003  (1)
July 2003  (3)
June 2003  (1)
May 2003  (1)
April 2003  (3)
March 2003  (2)
February 2003  (3)
January 2003  (5)
December 2002  (6)
November 2002  (5)
October 2002  (5)
September 2002  (4)
August 2002  (4)
July 2002  (3)
June 2002  (4)
May 2002  (9)
April 2002  (9)
March 2002  (10)
February 2002  (10)
January 2002  (3)
December 2001  (8)
November 2001  (1)
September 2001  (3)
August 2001  (11)
July 2001  (6)
June 2001  (2)
May 2001  (1)
April 2001  (20)
March 2001  (11)
February 2001  (12)
January 2001  (7)
December 2000  (12)
November 2000  (4)
October 2000  (9)
September 2000  (36)
August 2000  (7)
July 2000  (17)
June 2000  (19)
May 2000  (26)
April 2000  (11)
February 2000  (1)
January 2000  (1)
December 1999  (2)
November 1999  (7)
October 1999  (8)
September 1999  (17)
August 1999  (2)
July 1999  (3)
June 1999  (2)
May 1999  (1)
February 1999  (1)
October 1998  (4)
September 1998  (1)
May 1998  (1)
March 1998  (1)
January 1998  (1)
September 1997  (3)
August 1997  (1)
July 1997  (1)
April 1997  (1)
February 1997  (1)
December 1996  (1)
August 1996  (1)
July 1996  (1)
April 1996  (1)
January 1996  (2)
December 1995  (1)
September 1995  (3)
June 1995  (1)
February 1995  (1)
January 1994  (1)
September 1993  (2)
April 1993  (1)
May 1975  (1)
Categories
Alternatives
Announcement: Lectures Events & Radio Shows
Articles
Audio/Radio
Breaking Cases
Breaking News – Our Most Recent Serotonin Nightmares.
Celebrity Cases
DrugAwareness.org Newsletters
Education
Fda Testimony
Highly Publicized Cases
ICFDA Investigates
Journal Articles
Legal Cases
Ann Tracy on Health-Freedom Radio show
http://www.drugawareness.org/wp-content/uploads/2018-4-9-Your-Health-Freedom-Kristen-Chevrier-and-Lowell-Nelson-Ann-Blake-Tracy-Violence-and-Psychiatric-Drugs.mp3School shooting not ending!!! Protect your kid with the Ron Paul Home School Curriculum.
